brookes.ac.uk 2018-03-03

# Privacy policy - Oxford Brookes University

This website is operated by Oxford Brookes University which is registered with The Information Commisioner's Office as a data controller (registration no. Z6569324). As a provider of education and related services and facilities the university may collect and store personal information which you submit to the university via this website or via other means. This privacy policy explains how we use the personal information we collect.

## What information do we collect about you?

We collect information about you when you visit this website and voluntarily provide us with personal details in order to enquire about, apply for or access the courses, services and facilities we offer. You may choose to provide these personal details by completing an online form or by contacting us by email or by other means. We also collect information about how you use our website and what services you access.

**Cookies**

Information about your usage of our website is collected using cookies. See our cookie policy for further details.

**Session capture**

This website uses Mouseflow: a website analytics tool that provides session replay, heatmaps, funnels, form analytics, feedback campaigns, and similar features/functionality. Mouseflow may record your clicks, mouse movements, scrolling, pages visited and content, time on site, browser, operating system, device type (desktop/tablet/phone), screen resolution, visitor type (first time/returning), referrer, anonymized IP address, location (city/country), language, and similar meta data.

Mouseflow does not collect any information on pages where it is not installed, nor does it track or collect information outside your web browser. If you'd like to opt-out, you can do so at <https://mouseflow.com/opt-out>. 

If you'd like to obtain a copy of your data, make a correction, or have it erased, please contact us first or, as a secondary option, contact Mouseflow at [privacy@mouseflow.com](mailto:privacy@mouseflow.com "privacy@mouseflow.com").

For more information, see Mouseflow’s Privacy Policy at <http://mouseflow.com/privacy/>.

For more information on Mouseflow and GDPR, visit <https://mouseflow.com/gdpr>/.

**Phone**

When you contact the University by telephone we may record or monitor your telephone call for training and quality purposes.

## How will we use the information about you?

We collect and store information about you in order to respond to your enquiry or to process your application for our services or courses and, if you agree, to contact you about other services we offer which may be of interest to you.

We will also use the information we gather to improve your experience of using our website.

We will not share your information with third parties unless this is permitted or required by law or is otherwise indicated, for instance in our [cookie policy](https://www.brookes.ac.uk/About-Brookes/Structure-and-governance/policies-and-financial-statements/Cookie-policy/ "cookies policy").

## Access to your information and contacting us

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information that we hold about you.

If you would like a copy of the information we hold about you or if you have any questions about this privacy policy or how we handle your personal information, please email us at [info.sec@brookes.ac.uk](mailto:info.sec@brookes.ac.uk) or contact the Information Compliance Officer, Oxford Brookes University, Gipsy Lane, Oxford OX3 0BP.

## Other websites

Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website. When you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.

## Changes to our privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 10 February 2017.
